<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE node PUBLIC "-//freedesktop//DTD D-BUS Object Introspection 1.0//EN" "http://www.freedesktop.org/standards/dbus/1.0/introspect.dtd">
<node xmlns:doc="http://www.freedesktop.org/dbus/1.0/doc.dtd">
    <interface name="com.kylinsec.Kiran.Biometrics.Device">

        <method name="EnrollStart">
            <description>Start enrollemnt.</description>
        </method>

        <method name="EnrollStop">
            <description>Stop an on-going fingerprint enrollment started with EnrollStart.</description>
        </method>

        <method name="VerifyStart">
            <arg name="bid" direction="in" type="s">
                <description>Biometrics ID to verify against. Must have been previously enrolled with a device compatible to the device selected to perform the scan.</description>
            </arg>
            <description>Performs a new scan and verify it against a previously enrolled print.</description>
        </method>

        <method name="VerifyStop">
            <description>Stop an on-going fingerprint verification started with VerifyStart.</description>
        </method>

        <method name="IdentifyStart">
            <arg name="bids" direction="in" type="as">
                <description>A biometrics ID set to identify against. Must have been previously enrolled with a device compatible to the device selected to perform the scan.</description>
            </arg>
            <description>Performs a new scan and attempts to identify the scanned finger against a collection of previously enrolled fingerprints.</description>
        </method>

        <method name="IdentifyStop">
            <description>Stop an on-going fingerprint identification started with IdentifyStart.</description>
        </method>

        <property name="DeviceID" type="s" access="read">
            <description>The device id.</description>
        </property>

        <signal name="EnrollStatus">
            <arg name="bid" type="s">
                <description>Biometrics ID associate with finger data. Only valid if result is FP_ENROLL_RESULT_COMPLETE.</description>
            </arg>
            <arg name="result" type="i">
                <description>Represent the status of the enrollment. Refer to enum FPEnrollResult in biometrics-i.h.</description>
            </arg>
            <arg name="progress" type="i">
                <description>A number between 1 and 100 to describe the progress of enrolling fingerprint.</description>
            </arg>
        </signal>

        <signal name="VerifyStatus">
            <arg name="result" type="i">
                <description>Represent the status of the verification. Refer to enum FPVerifyResult in biometrics-i.h.</description>
            </arg>
        </signal>

        <signal name="IdentifyStatus">
            <arg name="bid" type="s">
                <description>The matched fingerprint. Only valid if result is FP_VERIFY_RESULT_MATCH.</description>
            </arg>
            <arg name="result" type="i">
                <description>Represent the status of the identification. Refer to enum FPVerifyResult in biometrics-i.h.</description>
            </arg>
        </signal>

    </interface>
</node>
